Richard Scarry Papers 1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993
  - Best Rainy Day Book Ever, 1974
    - Artwork and text (pages 148-49), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 472)
    - Artwork and text (pages 150-51), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 473)
    - Artwork and text (pages 152-53), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 474)
    - Artwork and text (pages 154-55), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 475)
    - Artwork and text (pages 156-57), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 476)
    - Artwork and text (pages 158-59), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 477)
    - Artwork and text (pages 160-61), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 478)
    - Artwork and text (pages 162-63), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 479)
    - Artwork and text (pages 164-65), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 480)
    - Artwork and text (pages 166-67), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 481)
    - Artwork and text (pages 168-69), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 482)
    - Artwork and text (pages 170-71), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 483)
    - Artwork and text (pages 172-73), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 484)
    - Artwork and text (pages 174-75), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 485)
    - Artwork and text (pages 176), ca. 1974 (Box OS:, Folder 486)
  - Best Workbook Ever Series, ca. 1986
    - Original black and white and color artwork (standard back cover), ca. 1986 (Box OS:, Folder 1295)
    - Fun with Numbers: Kindergarten, original black and white and color artwork (cover, 2 pieces), ca. 1986 (Box OS:, Folder 1296)
    - Fun with Numbers: Preschool, original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1986 (Box OS:, Folder 1297)
    - Fun with Numbers: Grade 1, original color artwork (cover), ca. 1986 (Box OS:, Folder 1298)
  - Clippings
    - Children's literature, general, 1979-1993 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
    - News items related to Scarry's books, 1971-1980 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
    - Scarry's life and writing, 1965-1994 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
    - Scarry's life and writing, ca. 1989? (Box OS:, Folder 1299)
  - Coloring books, original black and white and color artwork, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1300)
  - The Early Bird, 1968
    - Black and white and color separations (front end paper), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 590)
    - Black and white and color separations (title page), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 591)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 592)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 593)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 594)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 595)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 596)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 597)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 598)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 599)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 600)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 601)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 602)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 603)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 604)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 605)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 606)
    - Original black and white artwork (17 pieces), ca. 1968 (Box OS:, Folder 1301)
  - Early Words, 1976
    - Black and white, color, and text separations (front and back cover), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 607)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 608)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 609)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 610)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 611)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 612)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1976 (Box OS:, Folder 613)
  - Four Busy Word Books, 1982
    - Collection cover (black and white, color, and text separations), ca. 1982 (Box OS:, Folder 643)
    - Daddy Cat's Busy Day: Black and white, color, and text separations (cover-pages 15), ca. 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 644)
    - Huckle's Busy Day: Black and white, color, and text separations (cover-pages 15), ca. 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 645)
    - Lowly Worm's Busy ABC: Black and white, color, and text separations (cover-pages 15), ca. 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 646)
    - Sally and Mummy Cat's Busy Day: Black and white, color, and text separations (cover-pages 15), ca. 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 647)
    - Black and white separations (28 pieces), ca. 1982 (Box 8:, Folder 893)
    - Black and white separations (cover), ca. 1982 (Box OS:, Folder 895)
  - Funniest Storybook Ever, 1972
    - Original black and white artwork (32 pieces), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1232)
    - Black and white separations (cover), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1233)
    - Black and white separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1234)
    - Black and white separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1235)
    - Black and white separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1236)
    - Black and white separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1237)
    - Black and white separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1238)
    - Black and white separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1239)
    - Black and white separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1240)
    - Black and white separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1241)
    - Black and white separations (page 19), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1242)
    - Black and white separations (page 20), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1243)
    - Black and white separations (page 21), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1244)
    - Black and white separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1245)
    - Black and white separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1246)
    - Black and white separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1247)
    - Black and white separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1248)
    - Black and white separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1249)
    - Black and white separations (page 29), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1250)
    - Black and white separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1251)
    - Black and white separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1252)
    - Black and white separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1253)
    - Black and white separations (page 34), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1254)
    - Black and white separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1255)
    - Black and white separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1256)
    - Black and white separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1257)
    - Black and white separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1258)
    - Black and white separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1259)
    - Black and white separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1260)
    - Black and white separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1261)
    - Paste-ups (32 pieces), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1262)
    - Color separations (cover), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1263)
    - Color separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1264)
    - Color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1265)
    - Color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1266)
    - Color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1267)
    - Color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1268)
    - Color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1269)
    - Color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1270)
    - Color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1271)
    - Color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1272)
    - Color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1273)
    - Color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1274)
    - Color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1275)
    - Color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1276)
    - Color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1277)
    - Color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1278)
    - Color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1279)
    - Color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1280)
    - Color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1281)
    - Color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1282)
    - Color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1283)
    - Color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1284)
    - Color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1285)
    - Color separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1286)
    - Color separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1287)
    - Color separations (pages 52-53), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1288)
    - Color separations (pages 54-55), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1289)
    - Color separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1290)
    - Color separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1291)
    - Color separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1972 (Box OS:, Folder 1292)
  - The Great Auto Race (unpublished)
    - Dummy and copy, undated (Box 1:, Folder 27)
  - Great Big Air Book, 1971
    - Blueboard (cover) (Box OS:, Folder 716)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 717)
    - Color separation (alternate cover?), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 718)
    - Black and white and color separations (end papers), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 719)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 720)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 721)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 722)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 723)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 724)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 725)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 726)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 727)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 728)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 729)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 730)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 731)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 732)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 733)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 734)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 735)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 736)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 737)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 738)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 739)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 740)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 741)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 742)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 52-53), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 743)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 54-55), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 744)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 745)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 746)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 747)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 62-63; labelled 64-65), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 748)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 64-65), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 749)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 66-67), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 750)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 68-69), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 751)
    - Black and white and color separations (back cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 752)
    - Original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1091)
    - Original black and white artwork (end papers), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1092)
    - Original black and white artwork (page 4), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1093)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 6-7), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1094)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 8-9), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1095)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 10-11), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1096)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 12-13), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1097)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 14-5), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1098)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 16-17), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1099)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 18-19), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1100)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 20-21), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1101)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 22-23), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1102)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 24-25), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1103)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 26-27), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1104)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 28-29), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1105)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 30-31), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1106)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 32-33), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1107)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 34-35), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1108)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 36-37), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1109)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 38-39), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1110)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 40-41), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1111)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 42-43), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1112)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 44-45), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1113)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 46-47), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1114)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 48-49), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1115)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 50-51), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1116)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 52-53), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1117)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 54-55), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1118)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 56-57), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1119)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 58-59), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1120)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 60-61), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1121)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 62-63), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1122)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 64-65), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1123)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 66-67), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1124)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 68-69), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1125)
    - Original black and white artwork (back cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 1126)
  - Great Big Schoolhouse, 1969
    - Original acetate artwork (9 pieces), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 795)
      Pages 14-15, 18-21, 30-31, 40-41, 44-47, 56-57, and 68-69 only.
    - Black and white and color separations (title page, page 5), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 796)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 797)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 798)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 799)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 800)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 801)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 802)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 803)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 804)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 805)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 806)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 807)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 808)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 809)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 810)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 811)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 812)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 813)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 814)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 815)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 816)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 817)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 48-49), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 818)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 50-51), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 819)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 52-53), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 820)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 54-55), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 821)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 56-57), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 822)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 58-59), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 823)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 60-61), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 824)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 62-63), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 825)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 64-65), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 826)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 66-67), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 827)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 68-69), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 828)
    - Black and white and color separations (end papers and back cover), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 829)
  - The Great Pie Robbery, 1969
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 753)
    - Black and white and color separations (title page), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 754)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 755)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 8), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 756)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 9), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 757)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 758)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 759)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 760)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 761)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 762)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 763)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 22), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 764)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 23), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 765)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 24), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 766)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 25), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 767)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 768)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 28), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 769)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 29), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 770)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 30), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 771)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 31), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 772)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 32), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 773)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 33), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 774)
    - Black and white and color separations (page 34), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 775)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 6-7), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1217)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 8-9), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1218)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 10-11), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1219)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 12-13), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1220)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 14-15), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1221)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 16-17), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1222)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 18-19), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1223)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 20-21), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1224)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 22-23), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1225)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 24-25), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1226)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 26-27), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1227)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 28-29), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1228)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 30-31), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1229)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 30-31), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1230)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 32-33), ca. 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 1231)
  - The Great Steamboat Mystery, 1975
    - Original black and white artwork (17 pieces), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 830)
    - Black and white and color separations (cover), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 831)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 832)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 833)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 834)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 835)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 836)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 837)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 838)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 839)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 840)
    - Black and white and color separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 841)